{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Demon Slayer!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Tanjiro?",
      "answers": ["Slayer", "Demon", "Master"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Nezuko?",
      "answers": ["Demon", "Slayer", "Spirit"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Zenitsu?",
      "answers": ["Slayer", "Demon", "Healer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Nichirin?",
      "answers": ["Sword", "Shield", "Bow"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Inosuke?",
      "answers": ["Slayer", "Demon", "Mage"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Muzan?",
      "answers": ["Demon", "Slayer", "Angel"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Kanao?",
      "answers": ["Slayer", "Demon", "Priest"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hashira?",
      "answers": ["Pillar", "Group", "Leader"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rengoku?",
      "answers": ["Hashira", "Demon", "Swords"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Tamayo?",
      "answers": ["Demon", "Slayer", "Hunter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Genya?",
      "answers": ["Slayer", "Demon", "Mage"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Corps?",
      "answers": ["Group", "Sword", "Demon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Giyu?",
      "answers": ["Hashira", "Demon", "Cook"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kagaya?",
      "answers": ["Leader", "Demon", "Healer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Shinobu?",
      "answers": ["Hashira", "Demon", "Mage"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Urokodaki?",
      "answers": ["Master", "Demon", "Healer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Sabito?",
      "answers": ["Ghost", "Demon", "Mage"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Yushiro?",
      "answers": ["Demon", "Slayer", "Cook"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rui?",
      "answers": ["Demon", "Slayer", "Hunter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Sakonji?",
      "answers": ["Trainer", "Demon", "Scout"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
